(Sheldon:)building doodads with Wolowitz.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Amy:)Have you considered improving
your socialization skills,
(Amy:)thus allowing you
(Amy:)to communicate more
effectively with other people?
(Sheldon:)Isn't that their burden?
(Sheldon:)I'm the one with something
interesting to say.
(Amy:)Fair enough, but in its essence,
(Amy:)teaching is a performance art.
(Amy:)In the classroom paradigm,
(Amy:)the teacher has the
responsibility to communicate,
(Amy:)as well as entertain and engage.
(Sheldon:)I sense that you're trying
to slow-walk me to an epiphany.
(Sheldon:)Would you mind very much
jumping to it?
(Amy:)Perhaps you should consider
taking acting lessons.
(Amy:)Acting lessons.
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)It might help
if I could act as though I care
(Sheldon:)about my students
and whether or not they learn.
(Leonard:)Penny.
Penny. Penny.
(Sheldon:)What?
You're an "actress," correct?
I'm not an "actress."
(Penny:)I'm an actress.